Finding aid to the Classes of 1961-1970 records. CA.MS.01025
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1961-1970 records
1957-2010
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1961.
CA.MS.01025
22.833 linear feet (45 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together ten record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relevant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 1961-1970 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Smith College--Students.; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College. Class of 1962.; Smith College. Class of 1963.; Smith College. Class of 1964.; Smith College. Class of 1965.; Smith College. Class of 1966.; Smith College. Class of 1967.; Smith College. Class of 1968.; Smith College. Class of 1969.; Smith College. Class of 1970.; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College--Students.
- Class of 1961 Records, 1957-2002; 2.292 linear feet (6 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1961 was the eighty-third graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1961 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1961, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  - Commencement, 1961 (Box 2222, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Speech, 1961 (Box 2222, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1957 (Box 2222, Folder 3)
  - General, Groups, 1957-1961 (Box 2222, Folder 4)
  - Class Gift, 1961 (Box 2222, Folder 5)
  - Ivy Day, 1961 (Box 2222, Folder 6)
  - Class Letters, 1966-1977; 1995-2002 (Box 2222, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1966 (Box 2222, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Box 2222, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1976-1981 (Box 2222, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1986 (Box 2222, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 2001 (Box 2222, Folder 12)
  - Step Sings, 1961 (Box 2222, Folder 13)
  - Who's Who, 1957 (Box 2222, Folder 14)
  - Individuals, A-P (Box 2222.1)
  - Milly Margaret Freeman, class notes- art, history, Russian (Box 2223, Box 2224)
  - Ng'endo Mwangi (Florence), correspondence, Reto Medical Center (Box 2224.1)
  - Individuals, R-Z (Box 2225)
- Class of 1962 Records, 1958-2001; 5.125 linear feet (9 containers)
  The Class of 1962 was the eighty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1962 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1962, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1958 (Box 2226, Folder 3)
  - General, 1960-1962 (Box 2226, Folder 4)
  - Groups, 1958-1959 (Box 2226, Folder 5)
  - History, 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 6)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 7)
  - Ivy Day, 1962 (Box 2226, Folder 8)
  - Class Letters, 1966-1976 (Box 2226, Folder 9)
  - Class Letters, 1997-2001 (Box 2226, Folder 10)
  - Officers, 1959 (Box 2226, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 2226, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 2226, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1977 (Box 2226, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1982 (Box 2226, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1987 (Box 2226, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 2226, Folder 17)
  - Who's Who, 1958 (Box 2226, Folder 18)
  - Reunion, House newsletters (Box 2226.1)
  - Reunion memorabilia (Box 2226.2)
  - 35th and 40th Reunion photo albums (Box 2226.3)
  - Individuals, A-M (Box 2227)
  - Individuals, N-Z (Box 2227.1a)
  - Joan Sigel Schuman (Box 2227.1, Box 2227.2, Box 2227.3)
- Class of 1963 Records, 1959-2003; 2.667 linear feet (5 containers)
  The Class of 1963 was the eighty-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1963 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1963, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, questionnaires and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1963 (Box 2228, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1963 (Box 2228, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Music, 1963 (Box 2228, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1963 (Box 2228, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Day, 1959 (Box 2228, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1959 (Box 2228, Folder 6)
  - Ivy Day, 1963 (Box 2228, Folder 7)
  - Junior Ushers, 1962 (Box 2228, Folder 8)
  - Class Letters, 1966-1976; 2003 (Box 2228, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 2228, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1973 (Box 2228, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1978-1983 (Box 2228, Folder 12)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire Responses, 1978 (Box 2228, Folder 13)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire Responses, 1978 (Box 2228, Folder 14)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire Responses, 1978 (Box 2228, Folder 15)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire Responses, 1978 (Box 2228, Folder 16)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire Responses, 1978 (Box 2228, Folder 17)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire Responses, 1978 (Box 2228, Folder 18)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire Responses, 1978 (Box 2228, Folder 19)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2228, Folder 20)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2228, Folder 21)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2228, Folder 22)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2228, Folder 23)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2228, Folder 24)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2228, Folder 25)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 1)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 2)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 3)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 4)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 5)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 6)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 7)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 8)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 9)
  - Reunions-Surveys, 1993 (Box 2229, Folder 10)
  - Reunions-Newsletters, 1998 (Box 2229, Folder 11)
  - Reunion, 2003 (Box 2229, Folder 12)
  - Songs, 1963 (Box 2229, Folder 13)
  - Who's Who, 1959 (Box 2229, Folder 14)
  - Individuals, A-M (Box 2230)
  - Individuals, N-Z (Box 2230.1)
  - Susan G. Friebert, Art 13 scrapbooks (2) (Box 2230.2)
- Class of 1964 Records, 1960-2004; 0.833 linear feet (2 containers)
  The Class of 1964 was the eighty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1964 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1964, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Music, 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1960-1961 (Box 2231, Folder 4)
  - General, 1963-1964 (Box 2231, Folder 5)
  - Groups, 1960-1964 (Box 2231, Folder 6)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 7)
  - Ivy Day, 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 8)
  - Class Letters, 1966-1976 (Box 2231, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 2231, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 2231, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1979; 1984; 1999 (Box 2231, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 2231, Folder 13)
  - Reunions-25th Reunion Book, 1989 (Box 2231, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 2004 (Box 2231, Folder 15)
  - Who's Who, 1960 (Box 2231, Folder 16)
  - Individuals, A-C (Box 2231)
  - Individuals, D-Z (Box 2232)
- Class of 1965 Records, 1961-2010; 3.125 linear feet (5 containers)
  The Class of 1965 was the eighty-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1965 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1965, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1965 (Box 2233, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1965 (Box 2233, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1961-1962 (Box 2233, Folder 3)
  - General, 1963-1965; 1998 (Box 2233, Folder 4)
  - Groups, 1961; 1977 (Box 2233, Folder 5)
  - Hamper, undated (Box 2233, Folder 6)
  - Ivy Day, 1965 (Box 2233, Folder 7)
  - Junior Ushers, 1964 (Box 2233, Folder 8)
  - Class Letters, 1966-1980 (Box 2233, Folder 9)
  - Who's Who, 1961 (Box 2233, Folder 15)
  - Individuals, A-Z (Box 2233)
  - Sandra Blutman papers, 1963-1965 (Box 2233.1)
  - Reunion questionnaire, 1980 (Box 2234)
  - Reunions (Box 2235)
  - Reunions scrapbook (Box 2235.1)
- Class of 1966 Records, 1962-2006; 0.833 linear feet (3 containers)
  The Class of 1966 was the eighty-eighth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1966 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1966, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1962-1963 (Box 2236, Folder 4)
  - General, 1964 (Box 2236, Folder 5)
  - Groups, 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 6)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 7)
  - Ivy Day, 1966 (Box 2236, Folder 8)
  - Class Letters, 1967-1976 (Box 2236, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Box 2236, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1976-2006 (Box 2236, Folder 11)
  - Reunions-40th Reunion Survey Results [compiled], 2006 (Box 2236, Folder 12)
  - Who's Who, 1962 (Box 2236, Folder 13)
  - Individuals, A-L (Box 2236)
  - Individuals, M-Z (Box 2236.1)
  - 25th Reunion Book (Box 2237, Folder 1)
  - 50th Reunion Book (Box 2237, Folder 2)
- Class of 1967 Records, 1963-2002; 2.833 linear feet (5 containers)
  The Class of 1967 was the eighty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1967 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1967, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1965 (Box 2238, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1967 (Box 2238, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1967 (Box 2238, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1963-1964 (Box 2238, Folder 4)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1967 (Box 2238, Folder 5)
  - Ivy Day, 1967 (Box 2238, Folder 6)
  - Class Letters, 1968-1977 (Box 2238, Folder 7)
  - Class Newsletters, 1998-2001 (Box 2238, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 2238, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1977-1982 (Box 2238, Folder 10)
  - Reunions-Questionnaires/Results, 1977-1987 (Box 2238, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1987 (Box 2238, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 2238, Folder 13)
  - Reunions-Smithie Under a Tree, 1992 (Box 2238, Folder 14)
  - Reunions-30th Reunion Book and Newsletter, 1997 (Box 2238, Folder 15)
  - Reunions-Data and Disc, 2002 (Box 2238, Folder 16)
  - Reunions-Presentation Notes, 2002 (Box 2238, Folder 17)
  - Reunions-Text Copies, 2002 (Box 2238, Folder 18)
  - Senior Song, 1967 (Box 2238, Folder 19)
  - Who's Who, 1963 (Box 2238, Folder 20)
  - Yearbook, 1967 (Box 2238, Folder 21)
  - 35th Reunion questionnaire (Box 2238.1)
  - Individuals, A-Z (Box 2239)
  - Anne Wheelock, correspondence (Box 2240)
  - Beverly Jae Michajluk, memorabilia book (Box 2240.1)
- Class of 1968 Records, 1964-2003; 1.25 linear feet (3 containers)
  The Class of 1968 was the ninetieth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1968 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1968, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, undated (Box 2241, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1968 (Box 2241, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1968 (Box 2241, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1964-1965 (Box 2241, Folder 4)
  - Groups, 1964-1968 (Box 2241, Folder 5)
  - History, 1968 (Box 2241, Folder 6)
  - Hoop Roll, 1968 (Box 2241, Folder 7)
  - Ivy Day, 1968 (Box 2241, Folder 8)
  - Class Letters, 1969-1975 (Box 2241, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters-"Connections", 1995-2002 (Box 2241, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1973 (Box 2241, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1978-1983 (Box 2241, Folder 12)
  - Reunions-Reunion Yearbook, 1993 (Box 2241, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 2003 (Box 2241, Folder 14)
  - Senior Luncheon, 1968 (Box 2241, Folder 15)
  - Songs, 1968 (Box 2241, Folder 16)
  - Who's Who, 1964 (Box 2241, Folder 17)
  - Individuals, A-Z (Box 2242)
  - Ruth Eleanor Harwood manuscript (Box 2243)
- Class of 1969 Records, 1965-2005; 2.208 linear feet (3 containers)
  The Class of 1969 was the ninety-first graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1969 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1969, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1965 (Box 2244, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1969 (Box 2244, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1969 (Box 2244, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1965-1966 (Box 2244, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Song, 1965 (Box 2244, Folder 5)
  - Groups, 1969 (Box 2244, Folder 6)
  - Ivy Day, 1969 (Box 2244, Folder 7)
  - Junior Ushers, 1968 (Box 2244, Folder 8)
  - Class Letters, 1974-1976 (Box 2244, Folder 9)
  - Class Letters, 1997-2005 (Box 2244, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 2244, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1979-1984 (Box 2244, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 2244, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1994 (Box 2244, Folder 14)
  - Who's Who, 1965 (Box 2244, Folder 15)
  - Yearbook, 1969 (Box 2244, Folder 16)
  - Individuals, A-Z (Box 2245)
  - Rosalyn S. Zakheim, memorabilia book (Box 2245.1)
- Class of 1970 Records, 1966-2005; 1.667 linear feet (4 containers)
  The Class of 1970 was the ninety-second graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1970 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1970, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1970 (Box 2246, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1970 (Box 2246, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1970 (Box 2246, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1970 (Box 2246, Folder 4)
  - Directory, undated (Box 2246, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1966-1967 (Box 2246, Folder 6)
  - Groups, 1966-1968 (Box 2246, Folder 7)
  - Ivy Day, 1970 (Box 2246, Folder 8)
  - Last Chapel, 1970 (Box 2246, Folder 9)
  - Class Letters, 1969-1976 (Box 2246, Folder 10)
  - Class Letters, 2000 (Box 2246, Folder 11)
  - List of Majors, 1969 (Box 2246, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 2246, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1980 (Box 2246, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1985 (Box 2246, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1990 (Box 2246, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1995 (Box 2246, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 2005 (Box 2246, Folder 18)
  - Who's Who, 1966 (Box 2246, Folder 19)
  - Yearbook, 1970 (Box 2246, Folder 20)
  - Individuals, A-Z (Box 2247)
  - Elizabeth Singer- JYA France, photos, ephemera, coursework (Box 2247.1)
  - Elizabeth S. Estey slides, Class of 1970, Sept 1969-June 1970; 2017-A-0159; Estey, Elizabeth S., Class of 1970; 2 folders (2 envelopes in a box with multiple other accessions) (Box Shared)
    27 color slides of campus events, Ivy Day and Commencement 1970, and friends of Estey
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Donated by Elizabeth S. Estey, Class of 1970
    Slides